...No...
...Por favor...
¡No!
¡Senketsu!
Qué alivio.
¿Cuántas veces voy a tener que
cuidarte después de haberte desmayado?
¿Decidiste cambiar de carrera y convertirte en Nudista como yo?
Has una sola estúpida broma
más y será tu última.
Ah, lo siento, lo siento.
Así que, ¿quién te puso fuera de juego?
Fue Nui Harime. Nagita era Nui.
Oh, así que éso fue lo que pasó.
¿Me encontraste inconciente,
vestida de ésta manera?
Yeah. si hubiera llegado
a la escena un poco después,
habrías sido arrestada por la
policía por exposición indecente.
¿Tienes un último deseo?
¿Estamos susceptibles?
...Por supuesto estoy. Yo...
Perdí a Senketsu.
¿Con Nui Harime?
Así es. Fue cortado
en pedazos por ella.
Fuí debil y no pude obtener de
...nada de su poder, y fue destruído...
No estoy perdido.
Una sola más impresión como ésa
y realmente te asesinaré.
Hey, dame un respiro.
No dije nada.
Ryuuko, cálmate.
Ves, ¡lo haces de nuevo!
Lo tengo justo aquí.
Senketsu, ¡¿estás vivo?! ¡Estoy tan contenta!
Sólo porque me
tomaste tan fuertemente.
¿Y el resto?
¿Dónde está el resto de tí?
¿Las mangas? ¿Los hombros? ¿La falda?
¿H-Huh?
No ví nada más
cuando llegué ahí.
Sólamente tú, permanecías ahí inconciente,
aferrada a ése pedazo como su tu vida dependiera de ello.
Ryuuko, mi cuerpo destazado ha sido divido
entre los estudiantes del Viaje al Campo de Batalla.
Así que el resto de tí está en Kansai, huh?
Exactamente. Es obra de Satsuki Kiryuuin.
Diablos con ella.
¡Siempre se está metiendo en mi camino!
¿Huh? ¿Que hace un profesor como
usted aquí, Sr. Mikisugi?
Lamento decirlo, pero no
soy más un maestro.
El tiempo ha llegado.
Hoy, digo adiós a mi identidad encubierta como
el maestro titular de la Clase 2-A de la Adademia Honnouji.
¡Hoy, regreso a mi personalidad sin adornos!
Como uno de los desvestidos guerreros de Playa Nudista
que pelean contra la amenaza de las Fibras Vivientes:
un Espléndido Oficial Desnudo,
¡Aikurou Mikisugi! ¡Comencemos!
ESPLENDIDO OFICIAL DESNUDO
DE PLAYA NUDISTA
AIKUROU
MIKISUGI
¡Vamos, Estrella Fugaz Desnuda!
¡Adiós, estudiantes de la Adademia Honnouji!
¿De qué demonios se trató éso?
EPISODIO 14
CORRE COMO EL VIENTO
dareka ga katteni kimeta readymade na
Este es un mundo que esta disponible sólo para unos cuantos
kyou wo nugisutete
Me liberaré de sus grilletes
MATOI
RYUUKO
hadashi de hashitte iku
Y partiré hacia mi objetivo
IRA GAMAGOORI
machigattatte
Aún si pierdo el camino
IRA GAMAGOORI
UZU SANAGEYAMA
NONON JAKUZURE
HOUKA INUMUTA
korondatte
O tropiezo y caigo
HOUKA INUMUTA
FAMILIA MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MANKANSHOKU
surimuita itami mo
Esas heridas aún así forjarán
MAKO
MANKANSHOKU
AIKUROU
MIKISUGI
TSUMUGU
KINAGASE
original na ashita ni naru
Un futuro original para mí.
SATSUKI
KIRYUUIN
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
Yo forjo mi propio destino
chikai ga hikari ni natte
Y es cada vez más resplandeciente
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
Así que hasta el día que te alcance
naiteru hima nante nai kara
No tengo tiempo para sentarme a llorar.
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
Una ardiente pasión fluye desde mi
yozora de kagayaki dasu
Y brilla como estrella en el cielo nocturno
umarete kita imi ga
Creo que ahora entiendo
wakatta ki ga shita
Porqué naci.
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
Haré todos mis sueños realidad
kanaeru
Con mis propias manos.
He seleccionado estudiantes con tolerancia
alta a la Fibra Viviente,
y estoy distribuyendo las partes de la
Armadura Divina Senketsu entre ellos.
Seran añadidos a sus Uniformes Ultra
específicos del Viaje al Campo de Batalla,
y determinaré si es que pueden ser empleados
como un ítem de mejora que aumente el poder de sus habilidades.
Bien.
KYOTO
La Brigada de Viaje al Campo de Batalla de Kyoto
al mando de Nonon Jakuzure,
KOBE
la Brigada de Viaje al Campo de Batalla de Kobe Battlefield
al mando de Ira Gamagoori
y la Brigada de Viaje al Campo de Batalla de Osaka
al mando de Uzu Sanageyama
OSAKA
han llegado as sus
destinos específicos.
UNIDAD ESPECIAL
DE INTELIGENCIA
DE LAS TRES GRANDES CIUDADES
INUMUTA
HOUKA
Y la Unidad Especial de Inteligencia
de las Tres Grandes Ciudades espera también lista.
Ya nos hemos apoderado de los puertos
de información de las academias de cada ciudad.
Sus redes de información han sido aisladas,
y todas las conexiones telefónicas y de red
están bajo nuestro control.
Bien.
Esta operación colocará todas las escuelas preparatorias
de Kansai bajo nuestra sombra de un solo movimiento.
VIAJE AL CAMPO DE BATALLA POR LAS TRES GRANDES
¡Viaje al Campo de Batalla por las Tres Grandes, comienzen la operación!
¡Facción Armada de Preparatorias Kami-Kobe
Representante de la Alianza, Kyuuji Oobayashi!
REPRESENTANTE DE LA
ALIANZA DE ACCION DE
PREPARATORIAS KAMI-KOBE
KYUUJI
OOBAYASHI
REPRESENTANTE DE LA
ALIANZA DE ACCION DE
PREPARATORIAS KAMI-KOBE
KYUUJI
OOBAYASHI
REPRESENTANTE DE LA
ALIANZA DE ACCION DE
PREPARATORIAS KAMI-KOBE
KYUUJI
OOBAYASHI
REPRESENTANTE DE LA
ALIANZA DE ACCION DE
PREPARATORIAS KAMI-KOBE
KYUUJI
OOBAYASHI
REPRESENTANTE DE LA
ALIANZA DE ACCION DE
PREPARATORIAS KAMI-KOBE
KYUUJI
OOBAYASHI
¡Representante sustituto de la Facción
Armada de la Alianza, Kenta Sakuramiya!
REPRESENTANTE SUSTITUTO
DE LA FACCION ARMADA
DE LA ALIANZA
KENTA
SAKURAMIYA
REPRESENTANTE SUSTITUTO
DE LA FACCION ARMADA
DE LA ALIANZA
KENTA
SAKURAMIYA
REPRESENTANTE SUSTITUTO
DE LA FACCION ARMADA
DE LA ALIANZA
KENTA
SAKURAMIYA
REPRESENTANTE SUSTITUTO
DE LA FACCION ARMADA
DE LA ALIANZA
KENTA
SAKURAMIYA
REPRESENTANTE SUSTITUTO
DE LA FACCION ARMADA
DE LA ALIANZA
KENTA
SAKURAMIYA
REPRESENTANTE SUSTITUTO
DE LA FACCION ARMADA
DE LA ALIANZA
¡No los dejaremos dar un
sólo paso más allá de éste punto!
¡Cocteles Molotov! ¡A discreción!
¡Tenemos también ayuda de la escuela Americana!
¡Los sacaremos con el poder de sus
Cuerpos Armados de Fútbol Americano!
¡Sot Ira Gamagoori, Líder de la Brigada del Viaje al
Campo de Batalla de la Región Kobe de la Academia Honnouji!
LIDER DE BRIGADA DE
VIAJE AL CAMPO DE BATALLA
REGION KOBE
IRA
GAMAGOORI
¡Si establecen resistencia armada,
estamos preparados para responder de la misma manera!
¡Miembros del Buró Disciplinario
Mejorado, desplieguen!
¿Qué demonios?
¡Su sangre alimentará nuestro
equipamiento protector armado!
¡Todas las manos, a la carga!
¡Vamos!
¡Fuego!
¡Oh mi Dios!
...¡¿Qué demo...?!
¡Para un estudiante, las reglas escolares son
más pesadas que las piedras!
¡El Libro Guía de Disciplina en que estas reglas
están inscritas es más duro que el acero!
Libro Guía de Disciplina
de la Academia Honnouji
¡Las reglas escolares de la Adademia Honnouji
son como acero!
Libro Guía de Disciplina
de la Academia Honnouji
¡Reglas bañadas en acero!
Libro Guía de Disciplina
de la Academia Honnouji
¡¿Creen que esa armadura puede
soportar nuestras reglas cubiertas de acero?!
¡Prueben nuestro Huracán Metálico de Reglas del Libro Guía de Disciplina!
HURACAN METALICO DE REGLAS DEL LIBRO GUIA DE DISCIPLINA
¡I-Imposible!
¡¿Ahora pueden ver la potestad
de la Academia Honnouji?!
¡Éste es el poder de la Presidenta del
Consejo Estudiantil Satsuki Kiryuuin!
¡Todos, toquemos éste fortissimo!
NONON JAKUZURE
LIDER DE BRIGADA DEL
VIAJE AL CAMPO DE BATALLA
REGION KYOTO
¿De qué se trata ésto?
Bienvenidos, guerreros del Este.
¡La Academia Abekamo,
que ha permanecido por mil años
aquí en la antigua capital,
es el baluarte de las defensas de Kyoto!
Si desean evitar una muerte dolorosa,
dejen este lugar de inmediato.
Fallen en realizarlo, y serán bautizados
por una inundación de demonios y mounstros.
¡Escúchense, tratando de parecer grandes!
¡No hay ninguna escuela que
haya permanecido por mil años!
¿Qué son éstas cosas?
¡Son mounstros!
¡Van a comernos!
¡Estudiante guardián del Norte, Tarou Genbu!
ESTUDIANTE
GUARDIAN
DEL NORTE
TAROU
GENBU
¡Estudiante guardián del Sur,
Jirou Suzaku!
ESTUDIANTE
GUARDIAN
DEL SUR
JIROU
SUZAKU
¡Estudiante guardián del Este, Saburou Seiryu!
ESTUDIANTE
GUARDIAN
DEL ESTE
SABUROU SEIRYU
¡Estudiante guardián del Oeste,
Shirou Byakko!
ESTUDIANTE
GUARDIAN
DEL OESTE
SHIROU
BYAKKO
¿Lo ves?
Ésta es la Formación Divina de Cuatro,
¡la defensa impenetrable
de la Academia Abekamo!
¡Ustedes bárbaros de Kanto
no tienen esperanzas de derrotarla!
¿De qué es de lo que hablas?
¡Es tan obvio que éstos
mounstros son todos ilusiones!
¡Todos, cálmense!
¡Ésto es sólo un ataque psicológico!
What a fascinating bunch.
Would you mind if I
fought them for a while?
Inumuta?! I thought you were in Osaka!
What are you doing here?
Don't be startled.
This is merely a hologram projected by the Film Club.
Armed Arts Club! Advance!
This is a non-Euclidean space creation ritual calculated by the Math Club.
Art Club members, use this
as a basis for a Paradox Painting!
Our EM field! Impossible!
ESCHER
TOPOLOGY
ATTACK
An Escher Topology Attack.
What's that?
The Divine Four Formation employs geomagnetism to
envelop this location in special electromagnetic waves,
thereby disrupting the
nerve signals of the human brain.
The picture they just drew altered this area's
phase space and disrupted its geomagnetism!
In short, they have negated
the school's EM field!
I didn't understand a word of that,
but I guess when it comes to
obnoxious jerks, it takes one to beat one.
Then I guess this should be
your forte, should it not?
You uncouth boors and your strange words!
You leave us no choice but to fight!
This isn't my scene.
I'll leave them in your capable hands.
Thanks for nothing.
Okay, let's get jazzed up!
Armed Wind Instrument Club!
Combat Orchestration!
Pomp and Circumstance 'em!
I'm surprised you made it this far,
you pitiful Adademia Honnouji fleas.
NANIWA
KINMAN
HIGH
SCHOOL
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
TAKARADA
KANEO
I am the Naniwa Kinman High School
Student Council President, Takarada Kaneo!
You might've thought you were
hot stuff after Kobe and Kyoto,
but you ain't so tough here in Osaka!
Well, well, you've heard
what happened in the other cities?
BATTLEFIELD
TRIP
OSAKA
REGION
BRIGADE
LEADER
SANAGEYAMA
UZU
I thought we'd cut off
your information gateways.
I hate to break it to ya,
but I have powerful allies
in the form of Osakan grannies.
They'll spread gossip and rumors
in the blink of an eye.
Even if you lock down the net,
you can't stop gossipin' grandmas!
Now, listen close.
I'm gonna tell ya the rules of this town.
Osaka here is a merchant town!
It's money that
makes this town go 'round!
Whoever has the most cash wins!
Money? Philistine.
We have come to bring down those
like you who reek of the old system
in order to create the new world order
that Satsuki Kiryuuin strives to achieve!
You're adorable.
You naïve, naïve thing.
Don't start soapboxin' about society
until you learn how fearsome money can be.
Time to make you wake up to reality
by smackin' you in the face with wads of cash!
All right, men! Let 'em have it!
We're gonna kill ya!
Guns?
It's bills, sir!
They're shooting at us
with wads of bills as bullets!
They're literally using money as a weapon!
I put my money where my mouth is!
Get it? Then get lost!
Judging from the feel, these aren't
genuine Bank of Japan notes, are they?
Counterfeit bills, huh?
They ain't counterfeit!
They're Takarada Bucks!
Takarada Bucks?
Exactly. They're redeemable paper currency.
The word of the wealthy Takarada Conglomerate
is as good as gold here in Osaka.
They have more value than
our debt-ridden national currency.
But I guess a northern Kanto hick
like you wouldn't understand any of that!
How dare you!
If you go on mocking northern Kanto,
I'll grind you up with our konjac root harvest!
Not if we turn you jerks
into takoyaki first! Get 'em!
Armed Ping Pong Club!
Advance forward!
Sumo Club, advance forward!
Sumo Stomp Attack!
Armed Archery Club, Armed Track Club!
Ultra long range squads! Salvo attack!
Not bad, kiddo!
Now, storm the school building!
Over my dead body! Force 'em back!
You can stand against Ultima Uniforms?!
The Kiryuuins ain't the
only big players around here.
Don't underestimate the might of
the Takarada Conglomerate's money!
I'm gonna be heartbroken if I come all this way to Osaka
and all I get to do is this stupid ball bucket brigade!
...Hey, that's...
It's the veritable symbol of Osaka!
Jumbo takoyaki sold by a street vendor!
It just isn't a trip to Osaka
without eating some of those!
OSAKA
But I've got no money!
I got dragged here without knowing why,
so I'm flat broke right now! Penniless!
Boy, I sure wish somebody would
fire some money my way!
There is! There's a guy who's
spreading money around with a gun!
Bastard! I'm gonna send ya straight to Hell!
Not to Hell! I'm going straight to Heaven!
Go on, shoot me!
Don't you dare get between
Mankanshoku Mako and something she wants!
Who the hell are you?
...No way...
Bye!
Hey, gramps! Takoyaki, please!
I've got plenty of cash!
That's the Osaka-style okonomiyaki
that you eat with a spatula instead of chopsticks,
and that's kushikatsu,
where you're not allowed to double dip!
And ketsune udon, not kitsune!
And best of all is the butaman,
the ikayaki, the negiyaki, and more!
Now this is Osaka!
A Victory Road of food!
You are all that remain!
Attack!
Sorry, did I surprise you?!
Here's a little something
we had the Russian mafia smuggle in.
I don't know 'bout no Ultima Uniforms,
but can clothes stand up to a tank?!
Don't make me repeat myself!
Our ironclad rules will tear through
the armor of a mere tank as if it were paper!
How's this?!
The very latest iteration of Kobe's
specialty, composite meat armor!
KOBE SPECIALITY
COMPOSITE
MEAT ARMOR
Your "ironclad rules" or whatever get swallowed up by that
beautiful Kobe beef marbling and melt away into nothing!
Now, be a good boy and surrender, Gamagoori.
Laughable! If you think
you can make me, let's see you try!
Dumbass! Fire!
Fortified Disciplinary Unit, forward!
Discipline!
Oh crap! It's coming back!
That's hot! Hot!
Ow! It burns!
The meat's cooking! Yum!
It's so good!
These powered Godrobe patches certainly are something else.
Magnificent. Now, finish them!
So much for your final trump card.
Surrender peacefully, Oobayashi!
You! Matoi!
I came to get Senketsu back!
Lovely! What a beautiful sound!
With a Godrobe in our band,
we can play such beautiful music together!
I guess that about does it.
Transfer student!
What are you doing here?!
I don't have time to
mess around with you.
What's with that attitude?!
Why?
My bamboo sword is more
than enough for the likes of you!
It sounds like Gamagoori and Jakuzure have wrapped things up on their end.
How are you coming along?
Most of the Kinman High
students have been dealt with.
Tell Lady Satsuki that Osaka
will soon be under our control.
I wouldn't be so sure about that!
Takarada?
You underestimate my power, friend.
The students aren't my only pawns!
Thank you, come again!
How's business?! Not too bad!
You're making civilians
fight for you too, you bastard?
I am indeed.
But it's not quite accurate
to call them civilians.
They're all Combat Citizens
who have been blinded by money.
Everyone in this town
right now is just itchin' to fight!
They're tough!
That's the newest Osakan spot,
the Naniwa Sky Tower!
Right! Let's climb it!
When you see a high place,
you just get this irresistible urge to climb it!
How d'you like fightin' against Takarada Kaneo
and the "I Heart Osaka" Brigade?
If you want to take Osaka,
you'll have to kill every last one of us!
In the end, the real thing that
motivates people is cold, hard cash!
You "heart" it, eh?
What's the sense in
destroying your own city?
We'll just rebuild it afterward!
The contractors will love
all the extra work thrown their way!
Okay, people!
Kill that man, and I'll give you
a million Takarada Bucks!
Make him suffer!
So how are you gonna deal
with all these people, huh?
...That's—
What's that light?
L-Lady Satsuki!
...Ow...
Huh?
Hey, that's from Ryuuko's uniform, Senketsu!
Hey, you're Mankanshoku, the second-year!
What're you doing here?
You deserted in the face of the enemy
to go goofing around, didn't you?
What do you think the
Battlefield Trip is about, anyway?
Purge her!
I'm sorry!
Ryuuko!
I see you're taking things easy
and enjoying the sights of Osaka, Mako.
Boy, am I glad to see you, Ryuuko!
Senketsu's all chopped to bits!
Yeah, but I'll get him back.
I'll take back every last piece
and make him good as new.
Oh, I get it, Ryuuko.
You're going to all this trouble
'cause he's the only uniform you have.
There is only one left, Ryuuko.
Really? How are you feeling?
Rather well.
You've changed, don't you think?
How so?
The only part of me currently
supplying you with power is this scarf.
But even now, you're able to take down the
Ultima Uniforms augmented by my fragments in one strike.
You've become even stronger
than before, don't you think?
I'm getting stronger?
It's because what you desire
is almost in reach!
You're concentrating as hard as you can
on your desire to get Senketsu back to normal.
I get the same way, but with money!
Yeah, you concentrate pretty hard on that.
Of course! You can't spell "concentrate" without "cent", after all!
Okay, one to go.
Can you tell where it is, Senketsu?
...Yes, I can. However...
What is it?
The holder of the final fragment
is Satsuki Kiryuuin.
Satsuki? Seriously?
Fine. I'll get you back,
no matter who I have to face.
But in my current condition,
I cannot activate Life Fiber Synchronize mode.
How do you intend to
fight an opponent like Satsuki?
Don't worry. I'll pick up the slack.
I'm not the usual Ryuuko Matoi right now.
I'm concentrating everything I have,
now that my goal is almost within reach.
Isn't that right, Mako?
¡Yeah!
...Ryuuko...
¡Vengo por tí, Satsuki Kiryuuin!
chime ga naru mae ni
Antes de que suene la campana
kugurinuketa
Me escabullo de la escuela
otonatachi no haiiro no me
Esquivando las miradas vacías de los adultos
tawai no nai kaiwa
Las conversaciones sin sentido
togirenu mama
Simplemente continúan
sakamichi wo kudatteku
Mientras camino la pendiente.
nani wo suru demo naku
No tengo nada que hacer
yuku ate sae mo naku
Y ningún lugar donde ir.
tada atashi ima wa ne
En este momento, todo lo que hago
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Es ignorar cualquier advertencia
mada mada suki ni sasete
Porque aún quiero ser libre
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
Lo lamento, pero no va conmigo
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
Ser una estudiante ejemplar
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
Así que suelto dos botones de mi blusa
rojiura no nukemichi
Y tomo el negro callejón.
amai yuuwaku wa michi
Un camino de misteriosa dulce tentación
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
He mantenido algunas cosas ocultas a todos
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
Pero esta noche, te revelaré mis secretos.
AVANCES DEL SIGUIENTE EPISODIO
¡Osaka, un pueblo donde el dinero habla!
OSAKA
¡Osaka loca por el dinero!
¡En la búsqueda de su dispersada Armadura Divina Senketsu,
Ryuuko entra en la batalla!
DISPERSADA
ARMADURA DIVINA SENKETSU
¡¿Será la Armadura Divina Senketsu revivida al final?! Oh, cierto, ésa soy yo.
AL FINAL
ARMADURA DIVINA SENKETSU
SOY YO
La próxima en KILL la KILL,
"No me puedo contener"!
EPISODIO 15
NO ME PUEDO CONTENER